w3schools.com 2005-12-13

# About Privacy

* * *

## Privacy Statement for W3Schools

The following statements describes the privacy practices for W3Schools:

  * We do not collect any personal information from our users
  * IP addresses are logged for aggregate statistics and diagnosis
  * We only share aggregated statistics with our partners
  * Security settings protect the misuse of sensitive information
  * W3Schools does not use cookies to track any user information

* * *

## Personal User Information

W3Schools does not collect any information about its users or visitors.

Users are free to visit W3Schools, and navigate all its pages, without any user registration.

* * *

## Log Files

W3Schools uses IP addresses to diagnose server problems, analyze trends, administer the site, and gather demographic information for aggregate use.

IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

W3Schools only shares aggregated statistics with partners and advertisers. This information can not identify any individual person.

W3Schools has standard security measures in place to protect the loss and misuse of sensitive information.

* * *

## Cookies

W3Schools does not use cookies, but since we use ad companies to display ads, these ads might contain cookies. 

* * *

## Links

W3Schools contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This privacy document applies only to W3Schools.

* * *

## Contacting the Web Site

For any questions about this privacy statement, please contact:

* * *

* * *

## Product Spotlight

* * *

## Want To Be A Web Master?

If you want to be a Web Master, you will have to host your web site with an ISP (Internet Service Provider).

Founded in 1996 in North Carolina, AIT Inc. provides web hosting and ecommerce services to more than 190,000 domains in 107 countries. Shared, dedicated, and colocated hosting plans for both Linux and Windows users are available along with the industry's most lucrative reseller program. AIT has won acclaim as one of the fastest growing technology companies in North America by Inc. Magazine and by Deloitte & Touche.

As low as $39.95 per month for Dedicated Hosting! Choose from managed or fully managed options. Plans begin with an 80 GB hard drive and 1 terabyte of data transfer. AIT hosting packages are the ideal environment for web developers, designers, hosting resellers, entrepreneurs, and business IT departments to house your servers off site.

Visit AIT

* * *

## The Web Design Business Kit

Brendon Sinclair has a unique philosophy that everyone from Freelancers to the huge International Web Design Shops can learn from:

  * Your Web Design and Development skills don't matter!
  * You don't have to be the cheapest bidder to win!
  * Charging by the hour is the worst thing you can do!
  * Your clients are everywhere!
  * When the project finishes, your income should not!

Want to know more...?

|   
---|---  
  
* * *

* * *

## We Help You For Free. You Can Help Us!

  * Make a donation. Help us stay free.
  * Tell your newsgroup or mailing list.
  * Link to us from your pages.
  * Help us correct errors and broken links.
  * Help us with spelling and grammar.

* * *

Jump to: **Top of Page** or **HOME** or  **Printer friendly page**

* * *

## What Others Say About Us

Does the world know about us? Check out these places:

* * *

W3Schools provides material for training only. We do not warrant the correctness of its contents. The risk from using it lies entirely with the user. While using this site, you agree to have read and accepted our terms of use and privacy policy. 

Copyright 1999-2005 by Refsnes Data. All Rights Reserved.

* * *
